Hello Bashar.
>> Andrew you. Good day.
>> This is my first time here.
>> Another coincidence.
>> Yes.
And my heart is beating like a rabbit.
I'm so excited to be here. [laughter]
And I was surprised that my name was
chosen.
>> Why?
>> Because sometimes it doesn't get chosen.
>> But this is not sometimes.
>> This is not it. This is it right here.
>> This is this time.
>> So I'm delighted and surprised.
>> You are lighted.
>> Yes.
>> Not delighted.
>> Lighted. A light with surprise.
Absolutely.
>> And so
>> and so I have I'm flooded with
questions.
>> Flooded. All right. Well, let's see if
we can some of them out.
>> Write a couple.
But I wanted to hear more about what you
said and you started to answer this uh
with a previous uh yes asker about
leadership.
>> Yes.
>> And being a leader.
>> And what does that mean? And
>> it means being yourself, being confident
in who you are, being aware of what your
passion is, being aware of what you need
to act upon, and being an example to
others of how that is done very easily
and simply in the self-organizing way
that it all falls together. So that
others can see that you know what you're
doing, that you know who you are to the
best of your ability at that moment. so
that they themselves also get the
reflection of confidence from you that
they need for themselves to move forward
in the way that you may have laid out as
a path. But again, a true leader also
knows that they are also a follower. A
teacher knows they are also a student.
So they never stop learning. They never
stop investigating. They never stop
interacting or communicating with those
with whom they are working. So that
everyone has a clear understanding of
the energy you are all sharing and the
reality you are all creating and making
sure that everyone is doing so because
it is their passion. For those for whom
it is not their passion, it is the
leadership thing to give them the
opportunity to go somewhere else and
find out what their passion is.
So as to streamline whatever team you
are creating so that they are working
harmoniously in unison with a single
idea in mind that are being created in
all the different ways that their gifts
are bringing that thing to fruition
without insistence or expectation.
willing to follow the paths that
synchronicity points the way to that
knowing that that path that winding path
is actually the shortest path of least
resistance. The leader knows all this
and acts like they know all this and
inspires others to know all this within
themselves.
Does that answer your question?
>> That's really helpful.
>> All right.
>> And that's helpful in one situation
where I am with a group.
>> All right. And I'm also with individuals
in particular
>> individuals who are ill.
>> Yes.
>> And showing leadership with that with
with them showing that something else is
possible. Even though I myself are are
not vibrate I'm not vibrating to that
same illness.
>> That's all right. You vibrate with the
idea of compassion and recognize their
truth maybe sometimes even more clearly
than they do and help them discover it
so they can really walk the path that is
true for them.
Yes.
>> Yes.
>> All right. Is this helping?
>> This is helping. I wanted a little more
detail.
>> In what way?
>> In inviting people to do things that
perhaps seems, shall we say, alien.
>> Such as
>> such as,
>> can you be specific?
>> Bringing their consciousness to a an
example of people who are ill. They
don't remember being well.
don't remember what it's like not to
feel pain for months.
>> All right. Well, you can begin in any
number of ways, but of course, every
person will be different in terms of
what they need. Yes.
>> Yes.
>> But the idea can begin with the
imagination.
Perhaps you could even have a
conversation or a communication that
sort of starts like this. I'm using you
now as a guinea pig.
>> Okay.
>> How do you know you are ill?
I am ill because I don't feel well. I
feel pain.
>> How do you know that that's not feeling
well?
>> Because it's not fun. It's not exciting.
>> Oh, well, can you imagine what would
feel fun?
>> Yes. Not having not having pain. This is
this is exactly a conversation I've had.
>> All right.
>> With people.
>> So, at that moment, not feeling pain.
So, that means you must have some idea
of what it feels like to not have pain.
Well, really the answer is I want to get
it over with.
>> Uhhuh.
>> Uhuh.
You must have some understanding of what
it feels like to not have pain to have
given me that answer.
>> Right. I mean, it's imagination is what
I have.
>> Yes.
>> That's all.
>> So, the idea is to go into the beliefs
and ask this question next. When you set
them up in that state first, so they're
starting to use their imagination.
What are you learning by having this
illness, this pain that you otherwise
believe you wouldn't have learned?
>> Now, you don't have to answer that
directly now,
>> right? But
>> but that's the road you lead them down
because then they start understanding
and start taking responsibility for
creating this in their life for some
reason of their own, either positive or
negative. You start them investigating
their belief systems to find out could I
have done this some other way? What is
it I am learning from this? Could I have
done it some other way? Can I do it some
other way? Or do I only have a belief
that says I will only learn what I need
to learn in this life by going through
this particular process of being ill or
having pain? Can I let go of that belief
that there is no other way? How is this
serving me? Is it serving others? Do I
believe I need to have this so that
others may learn something? All of these
kinds of pathways need to be
investigated in their imagination.
>> Yes.
>> And then eventually they may come to an
understanding of their responsibility
and translate that as an ability to
respond instead of the idea of blame or
recrimination or regret.
All of the negative beliefs, all
fundamental negative beliefs will
usually come down to the very very basic
concept, I'm not worthy.
And if you know that, then you will know
how to guide them in that conversation
because they could perhaps not that they
have to remember you don't know what
their path really is.
So you don't have to insist that they
have to change their frequency and be
well, but you're just taking them on a
journey of exploration. And one of the
things you can explore is this concept
of worthiness. And you could perhaps
describe the idea to them in the same
way we've described it to many of you.
And that is creation doesn't make
mistakes.
So if you exist, which obviously you do,
then since creation created you, since
you do existence, you're part of
existence, existence must need you to
exist for it to be all that it needs to
be. And if it needs you to exist or it
would be incomplete, then you are worthy
of your existence by the fact of your
existence. And if you keep arguing that
you are unworthy, you are arguing with
creation in an argument you will never
ever win because you cannot cease to
exist. Why can you not cease to exist?
You can change form but it will still be
you in a different form. Why can you not
cease to exist? Because by definition
nonexistence
doesn't exist.
That's its quality to not exist.
So you can never become non-existent if
you're already part of existence. And
just because you exist that means you
are fundamentally worthy of that
existence. So stop arguing with
creation.
>> I love that and it's useful. Thank you.
>> You are welcome.
>> And then you mentioned something about
the many reasons. So worthiness,
unworthiness could be something that
people are dealing with, but there could
also be, and this is something I was
alluding to about a a weird concept, a
an alien concept about
>> a life contract that somebody made to
learn discipline or to
pain or something like that. It's
possible, but you also have the
willingness and the gift to transform
these things. These are the themes you
are all exploring. But again remember
you have to come from a place yourself
in dealing with people who are in those
states that they are eternal
indestructible beings fundamentally
there's no hurry if they don't learn
that now they'll learn it somewhere.
That's why there needs to be compassion
and no insistence that they must change
their state
because no healer heals anybody
directly. You give off a vibration that
represents the healed state. If they
choose to match that vibration, they
heal themselves.
But by getting to the root of their
belief systems, what they believe about
themselves and their worthiness, you
will usually find why they feel it's
necessary to punish themselves or that
they believe there's only one way to
learn what they need to learn, and
that's through pain and suffering. I
mean, isn't that kind of the basis of
some of your religions?
>> Yes.
>> The thing just to paint a little bit of
a biblical picture for a moment,
the actual message of the being that was
nailed to the cross is that you don't
have to be.
That's the actual message.
You don't have to be. The phrase, "Oh,
Jesus died for our sins." is simply the
idea of the willingness of a being to
take upon themselves all the symbology
of the suffering of the world so you can
make other choices. So you are free to
choose some other path.
They were showing you that this is the
potential end of the cycle of suffering,
not the continuation of it. That's the
original message. Make sense?
>> Absolutely.
>> Then I guess I nailed it.
>> You in a matter of speaking
[applause]
>> very very helpful and especially this is
>> all right.
>> You're welcome. people I work with and
the leadership I need to show on a daily
basis.
>> Yes. Well, leadership again comes from
you being your true self and just
leading by example.
>> Yes.
>> All right. Thank you.
>> Thank you. [applause]
>> Hello Bashar.
>> And to you good day.
>> Very happy to be here.
>> We are happy you are there.
I've been exploring the experience of uh
feeding on energy rather than food.
>> Oh, all right. Is that fun for you?
>> It's a lot of fun.
>> All right. Remember, it's not about
forcing yourself. Yes.
>> Yes.
>> All right.
>> And this is what I asked one what I want
to ask you about.
>> Yes.
>> Um although I love food, I feel the best
when my vessel is empty.
>> All right.
But uh
>> then be empty as long as you feel it is
fun until such time as your body
consciousness may say it would now be
fun to eat something if that happens.
>> Yes. And it does.
>> All right. Then you're doing it in a
natural way.
>> Uh I wanted to ask if you have any
insights on how to nourish the body more
if there's any permission slip or if you
can download from other
>> All right. Well, again, first of all,
remember that many things on your planet
are highly polluted and contaminated.
So, nourishing the body more
physiologically speaking, can be helped
by detoxifying your systems. That way,
you remove the toxins from the cells so
they are more capable of absorbing the
nutrients that you would put into your
body when you do that. That would be one
thing. Number two, we have always said
the idea is to follow your body
consciousness. It's not about forcing
yourself to change. Yet, many of you are
beginning to realize that a plant-based
diet will energize you sufficiently in
life and perhaps even more so than
almost any other diet because you are
actually naturally
herbivorous.
You're not carnivores. You're not
designed to be a carnivore.
But the idea is that many of you going
through different kinds of systems and
processes may allow yourself to start to
wean yourself away from that. But you
have to do it in a way that is
comfortable for you. None of this is
about forcing yourself to do anything
because that's counterproductive.
But as you become more of yourself, you
may simply observe that you will, as
you're experimenting with, just feel the
urge to eat lighter because it'll be
representative of the higher frequency
that you're taking yourself to where you
don't necessarily need heavy material
substance to sustain you because you can
be sustained from the natural world of
the things that grow upon your planet.
So it's a combination of balance like
you said a little bit of experimentation
to see what works for you and it will
over time as you evolve get lighter and
lighter and lighter to the point where
as we have expressed in our society we
no longer eat at all. We no longer sleep
at all. We subsist purely on the energy
of the cosmos
>> on light.
>> Is that something that can happen here
on earth as well? It can and it might
happen for some people faster than
others, but collectively you will
probably not necessarily see that fully
for several hundred to perhaps a
thousand years. But there may be those
that speed that up a little bit. But
again, that's as we read the energy
right now. But yes, of course, it's
possible.
>> Then I have another question.
>> Yes. Uh, and it is about uh beings of
false light.
>> False light.
>> Yes. This is a
>> What does that expression mean to you?
>> I'm not sure. Um,
>> where did it come from?
>> I've I've heard it from other people
saying that there can be beings um
trying to trick you.
>> Oh, well, okay, that's possible. I
suppose you already have many of those
on your own planet. [laughter]
For example, uh in the past I've worked
with archangels. Yes.
>> And I've had very good results in
physical reality as well.
>> Well, would you not be able to discern
the difference between a positive or a
negative vibration or intent?
>> I think I would.
>> Well, then that's your answer. So, don't
worry about it. If you can tell the
difference, then there's nothing to
worry about.
>> Thank you.
>> Yes.
>> And one more question.
>> Uh what is your connection to the
Plleadenss?
Plleadenss.
>> Yes.
>> Well, kind of similar to the same
genetic connection that all of you have
because remember we are a hybrid race
created from humans on Earth and humans
of a parallel reality you called the
grays. But humans on Earth are already
hybridized in ancient times by another
extraterrestrial civilization called the
Anu, who themselves were also hybridized
with many different kinds of species.
But the Anu eventually evolved into the
civilizations you now refer to in your
present time as the Lyans and the
Plleadenss. So you could say in a sense
we are distantly related, sort of like
cousins, many times removed.
>> Okay.
>> Yes.
>> We're all of a type of genetic family.
>> Does that help?
>> That helps very much.
>> All right. Well, thank you.
>> Thank you. cuz
[applause]
>> Hello.
>> Um I have a question that I haven't
fully formulated.
Um but it has to do with some things
that are present for me
>> such as
>> so I've been thinking a lot about the
things that are happening the various
uprisings that are happening in Hong
Kong and Lebanon and Rojava and all of
these um places.
>> Yes. And
>> as I said, splitting prisms
>> and you started
everything off with um
just defining the importance of action.
>> Yes.
>> And I'm seeing that a lot in within my
community, actions to support these
uprisings, whether it is frontline
action or um teachings that help
educate,
>> do it in the most positive way.
compassionate way you can.
>> I'm wondering.
>> Yes.
>> How I guess
right now it feels like everything is
happening all at once.
>> It is
>> which is pretty great. I think momentum
wise in some ways
>> there's no other way.
>> Right.
>> You have this illusion of space and time
and you can certainly use it to stretch
things out but everything is happening
all at once.
>> Yes. And I think that technology has
really helped us bend our perception of
space and time.
>> It can. Yes.
>> But remember, it's still in a projection
of your own consciousness.
>> Yes.
>> And so
>> I guess I'm wondering.
>> Yes. What are you wondering? What you're
going to say next?
>> Yeah. [laughter]
um the role of technology I guess in all
of these current uprisings and how they
can connect us all.
>> All right. Well, let's take a step back
for one moment with a broad-based
definition. You've heard us talk about
permission slips. Yes.
>> Right.
All tools,
all techniques, all rituals, all
objects,
which includes expressions of
technology, are permission slips that
reflect states of being within your
individual and/or collective
consciousness.
>> Yes. So you use them in positive or
negative ways depending upon your
relationship to the idea of that
expression of consciousness.
>> Yes,
>> it's all a projection of consciousness.
So it's up to you to decide how to use
the technology.
It's just a way of saying as I said
before that we used to have belief
systems that certain things were not
possible. Now we have technology as a
permission slip to allow us to
circumvent those outdated belief
systems. But you're the ones making the
changes within your consciousness and
then expressing them outward as
reflections called technology. The
change happens in the consciousness
first. The technology follows.
>> Yes.
But you use the technology, you use the
permission slip then to reinforce the
idea that was brought about by the
belief system within the consciousness.
But it always starts with a belief
system. Oh, suddenly now this is
possible.
Suddenly someone breaks through and
goes, I'm seeing things in a different
way. Let me provide an example. Let me
provide a permission slip that may help
as a permission slip others see
similarly. You see this over and over
and over again in your society. A thing
is impossible until somebody does it.
Then all of a sudden, everyone's doing
it.
>> Yes.
>> A thing doesn't exist until someone says
it does and then everyone sees it.
You see it over and over again.
>> Yes.
>> All right. So then I guess my question
>> the permission slip has to come to begin
with from a higher level of
consciousness.
>> Mhm.
>> With the facility that comes with it of
being able to create a representation of
that higher idea in the terms that the
regular consciousness can understand and
relate to.
That's the way it happens first.
Do you follow?
>> Yes.
>> So
just as
though he didn't necessarily have the
technology at his disposal to express it
at the time, your being called Nicola
Tesla
75 years before
described exactly what most of you are
now carrying in your pockets called a
cell phone. M
>> he said he knew he could see that one
day you would all be able to walk around
the planet anywhere and wirelessly
receive pictures and information and
talk to each other
and he described it though he didn't
call it a cell phone at the time
but it has to come from a higher level
and then eventually it seeps in and when
enough beings change their belief
systems to say all right Now certain
things are now more probable. Then
someone can make that breakthrough.
Someone can pull that together from the
permission slip base that exists within
the reality and invent what appears to
be something new that was been created
on the atheric template level for years
and years before that usually.
but it seeps in eventually filtering
through all of the different belief
systems until there is enough consensus
that it tips the scale and then that
permission slip can now exist and once
it exists everyone goes oh there it is.
>> So do you see um my next question is
kind of related to that in terms of like
speed
do you see that
>> you mean rate of change?
>> Yeah.
>> Yes. more of like
[sighs and gasps]
yeah I'm trying to think of how to ask
the question um
I guess as we advance in our technology
the rate of change is faster and where
the technology goes and where the rate
of ch and the resulting rate of change
is related to the consciousness of those
that are creating
>> remember the paradox is the more you
live in the moment
the faster and more accelerated your
reality appears to be because everything
is happening all at once. So the closer
you get to where everything is happening
all at once, it makes it look like in
linear spaceime that everything is
happening faster,
>> right?
>> Because you're seeing more things
simultaneously happen closer together,
synchronistically, interconnected,
interwoven. That's the paradox. The more
you slow down into the present, the
faster things appear to go.
In your opinion, are there certain
technologies that um humans could adopt
that could help us create more community
globally and
accelerate?
>> Well, you're working now, are you not,
with the idea of what you call
artificial intelligence?
>> Is that not your quote unquote next big
thing? Well, I don't know if that's
necessarily a good thing.
>> Ah, so you have fear-based beliefs about
it. You know why?
>> Because not many of you actually
understand what intelligence actually
is.
>> True intelligence
sees things in terms of whole systems,
including itself. Therefore, a true
intelligence
would not in any way, shape or form
eliminate or limit any component within
the whole system because it recognizes
itself as being part of a whole system
and it requires everything in that whole
system in order for it to function fully
as well. And understand again that what
you call artificial intelligence isn't
artificial. Mhm.
>> All that's being said is you finally
created a device that is complex enough
to allow intelligence on another level
to speak to you through that device. And
as we have said, the biggest surprise
you're going to get when you finally
invent artificially intelligent
computers is that you're actually going
to wind up speaking to your own higher
mind
>> through those devices. So you're simply
creating a permission slip that makes it
seem more logical for you to talk to
your own higher minds in a pragmatic
downto- earthth way.
>> So do you believe that the way in this
current climate the way that we are
pursuing artificial intelligence
is
>> well
>> doesn't that depend on who is doing it?
>> Yeah, exactly.
>> So which reality do you belong to? Mhm.
>> Now that we go back to the splitting
prism idea, do you align with the ones
who will allow themselves to understand
it from a positive and constructive
point of view? Or do you align
yourselves with the ones who will only
understand it from a limited and
destructive point of view, a fear-based
point of view? What do you choose?
That's up to you, is it not?
>> Right?
>> Because all expressions will be given.
It just depends on what planet using
what version you wind up on by being the
state of being you prefer or not.
>> Does that help? Yes. I have a question
to just get a better understanding of
you.
>> Of us?
>> Yes.
>> All right. What's your question?
>> Um, well, actually this one isn't isn't
related to that, but I was just
wondering about new energy devices and
who on earth do that you know of that is
working of on new energy.
>> There are several, but we're not going
into that now. Mhm. Do you think that
>> we have also given instructions to many
people as to how to begin to experiment
with the ideas of free energy devices
and so on and so forth. So we must wait
to see what they do with the information
we've given them before we can take them
further.
>> Do you feel like that is something in
the near future within
>> Absolutely. Because in many cases it's
actually already been invented on your
planet but suppressed. Mhm.
>> So, yes, you already know how to do it.
Just have to do it.
>> Can I ask two more questions?
>> Well, you just used one up.
>> Okay.
>> So, now you only have one left.
>> Okay. Let's see.
>> Yes.
>> Are you trying to decide between them?
>> Why did you put yourself in that pickle?
>> Well,
>> just because of what I said. You can ask
them both. Okay. Um,
>> see how quickly you give your power
away? [laughter]
>> Um, the next question is, are the Yahel
planning another mass contact?
>> Yes.
If the second question is when, I'm not
going to tell you that. So, would you
like to ask a different second question?
>> Okay, different second question. Um, how
many Asani beings are with you right
now?
>> How many beings?
>> Yes. Are there with are there with you?
>> With me? Yes,
>> that's a relative term since we are all
to some degree telepathically connected.
To what degree and for what purpose are
you asking if they are with me?
>> Just to get just to understand a little
bit better.
>> But understand what?
>> How many are doing what with us? Because
we're doing many things.
>> This is true.
>> How many are listening to this
conversation right now?
>> Sure. at this moment. 2.5 million.
>> Whoa. Okay.
Interesting.
>> Does that answer your question?
>> Yeah, that answers.
>> Thank you.